（忆往昔）
1967年4月21日
On April 21, 1967,
第一亿辆通用汽车
the 100 millionth GM vehicle.
在简斯维尔的工厂生产下线
rolled off the line at the plant in Janesville …
三天之后 另一辆车在同一生产线上下线
Three days later, another car rolled off that same line.
这辆1967年款的雪佛兰英帕拉
This 1967 Chevrolet Impala.
将会成为世上最重要的车…
would turn out to be the most important object …
成为整个宇宙的重中之重
in pretty much the whole universe.
听听她的声音
Listen to her purr.
这才是你想要的车
this is the car you want.
是吗 你对车很有研究吗
Oh, yeah? You know something about cars?
关于车的知识 都是我父亲教我的
My dad taught me everything about cars.
我知道我很久没祈祷了
I know it's been a long time…
迪恩和我 我们经历了很多坏事
Dean and I, we've… we've been through a lot of bad.
但这次不一样
But this is different.
这次是我的错 我不知道该怎么补救
This is my fault, and I don't know how to fix it.
我们需要帮助 上帝
we need your help, God.
我们需要知道希望尚存
We need to know there's hope.
（如今）
（萨·温 迪·温）
[邪恶力量 第11季第4集]
（48小时前）
哥们 短裤是闹哪样啊
Dude, what's up with the shorts?
这地堡下面是自由世界
It's a free bunker.
有发现吗
Did you find anything?
关于黑暗 没有
Not on the Darkness. No.
梅塔特隆呢
What about Metatron?
还是不见踪影 没有线索
Still in the wind. No leads.
这可好
Great.
外面有个古老的邪恶
So we have an ancient evil out there somewhere,
每天都愈发强大
Just getting stronger by the day.
小卡在好转了 这是好事
Cass is getting better, so there's that.
还想帮你治好…
Still wants to fix your, uh…
我没事 百分百没事
I'm fine. Fine. 100%.
好吧 他还没百分百呢
All right, well, he's not.
还需要时间疗伤
He still needs more time to heal.
好吧
Well…
看来我们只能慢慢等着疗伤了
Guess we got nothing to do but get better.
我不知道你怎么样 但是
I don't know about you, but…
我是憋出严重的幽居病了
I've got some serious cabin fever.
这里的车我都洗过两次了
I've washed every car in here twice.
我可能找到桩案子
Well, I may have found us a case.
- 虽然不太靠谱 - 那也成啊
- I mean, it's thin… - Hey, thin works.
路上说
Tell me on the way.
就知道一洗车就下雨
Figures.
好了 说吧 什么情况
All right, let's hear it. What do you got?
俄勒冈州 尤金市外的贵格会谷镇
Okay, uh, Quaker Valley, Oregon, town outside of Eugene.
德怀恩·马克汉姆 当地治安官
DWayne Markham, the local sheriff,
几日前在林中被人发现
was found in the woods a couple days ago.
尸体被残害
His body was mauled,
于是被认为是动物袭击
so they chalked it up to an animal attack,
- 但我想可能是… - 狼人
- but I'm thinking… - Werewolf.
- 嗯 可能吧 - 是啊 的确不太靠谱
- Yeah, maybe. - Yeah, you're right. That is thin.
是啊 可能不是案子 是吧
Yeah. Probably nothing, right?
可能吧 俄勒冈州 我们来了
Probably not. Oregon, here we come.
那是什么
What is that?
是冰沙
It's a smoothie.
啤酒呢
Where's the beer?
冰沙下面呢
Under the smoothies.
其他的啤酒呢
Where's the rest of the beer?
小卡
Ooh, it's Cass.
- 我们得接 - 拜托
- We gotta… we gotta… I gotta get this. - Man.
小卡 没事吧
Hey, Cass. Everything all right?
嗯 我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
我刚在看你们要去的那一带的
I was just reading up about the other cases.
其他案件
in the area that you're headed to.
还没发现符合这些特征的东西
I haven't found anything yet that matches.
小卡 你只有一项任务 就是疗伤
Cass, you've got one job to do and that's to heal.
- 明白了吗 - 我能帮忙
- You understand? - I can help.
当然了 小卡
Yeah, of course you can, Cass,
但现在 你该专注于好起来
But right now is the time for you to focus on getting better.
这只是小菜一碟 我们能行的 所以
This is just a milk run. We got it. So…
- 尽量放松一下吧 - 好吧
- Try and relax. - All right.
读本书 看看网飞什么的
Read a book, watch some netflix.
那是什么
What's a netflix?
去我屋 打开电视 你会明白的
Go to my room, turn on the tv. You'll figure it out.
好吧 有事打给我
All right. Just call if you need anything.
好啊 小卡 谢啦
Got it, Cass. Thanks.
你觉得他会没事吗
You think he's gonna be okay?
他就是需要时间
He just needs some time, you know?
我们都是
We all do.
你不是吧
Are you serious?
迪恩 都多晚了 我累死了 也饿死了
Dean, it's late. I'm exhausted and… and… and starving.
这地方…
And this place…
就连史威兹都不会到这种旅馆来
I mean, even Swayze wouldn't come to this roadhouse.
首先 永远别乱用史威兹的大名
Okay, first of all, never use Swayze's name in vain.
好吗 永远不要
Okay? Ever.
其次 你不记得这里了吗
Second, you don't remember this place?
不记得海瑟了吗
You don't remember Heather?
几年前跟我们一起合作温迪戈案子的
The hunter that we worked a wendigo case.
- 那个猎人 - 是啊
- a couple years ago? - Oh, yeah.
- 是啊 - 她今晚在吗
- Yeah, exactly. - What, she's here tonight?
我给她发了短信
I texted her.
她在德州办个法国狼人的案子
She's working a rugaru case in Texas.
实际上 她没回我短信 但那不是重点
Actually, she never texted me back. That's not the point.
重点是 我们还要开很久呢
The point is, is that we have a ton of driving left to do.
就为了去个可能根本没案子的小镇
just to go to a town where there's probably not a case.
但那里面 有快乐时光
But in there…Good times.
时间能治愈一切伤口 萨姆
And time heals all wounds, Sam,
尤其是快乐的时光
especially good times.
怎么样
What do you say?
我说 你自便吧
I say, knock yourself out.
我要去找个餐馆 像小卡那样查查传说
I'm gonna find a diner, dig into the lore like Cass did,
看看我们要去的地方有没有什么事发生过
see if anything's ever happened where we're headed.
老天 你真得学会找乐子
Oh, man, you really gotta learn to have fun.
真的 太可悲了
Seriously, it's pathetic.
真不该去
Mistakes were made.
你是谁
Who are you?
早上好
Uh, good morning.
这是我哥哥迪恩
That's, uh, my brother Dean.
抱歉 萨姆 我不…
Sorry, Sam, I didn't…
我不知道你有客人
I didn't realize you had company.
嗯 能给我们点时间吗
Yeah. Yeah, uh, could you give us a minute?
我…先出去了
Well, I'll just, uh… Just won't be here anymore.
你们慢慢来吧
So you kids take your time.
你看到我的发夹了吗
Have you seen my hairpin?
迪恩 我可以解释怎么回事
Dean, I can explain what was going on…
不用
No, no, no. No.
别放《夜行客》嘲笑我
Don't "Night Moves" me.
让歌声洗刷你
Just let it wash over you.
听我说
Look…
沉浸其中吧
Just take it in.
简直荒谬
This is ridiculous.
史上最伟大的摇滚乐手之一啊 萨穆埃尔
One of the greatest rock writers of all time, Samuel.
是萨姆
It's Sam.
*在我哥哥67款雪佛兰的后座上*
*Out in the backseat of my brother's '67 Chevy*
是你挑的头 你挑的头
Yeah, you started this. You started this.
好了 一起来
Here we go. Come on now.
*趁着夜色练习动作*
*Workin' on our night moves*
下次我来选
Next time, I choose.
- 别碰方向盘 - 你都没看路
- Hands off the wheel. - You're not even looking at the road.
查查传说
"Digging into tho lore."
如今的孩子都这么个说法啦
Is that what the kids are calling it these days?
我真需要那个
Man, I needed that.
瞧啊
And hey, look at that,
你终于破处了
you're finally not a virgin anymore.
但知道吗 我觉得也是时候了
But you know what? I think it was time.
我尊重你
I respect the fact that you, uh, you know,
想要保持纯真 等待真爱
you wanted to stay true and pure and waited.
告诉你 你就是个白痴
Yeah, you know what? You… you're an idiot.
还铺了毯子
Even put a blanket down.
哥们 总是那么有风度又体贴
Buddy, classy and thoughtful as always.
我还想把我的号码给她
I tried to give her my number.
知道她说什么吗
You know what she said?
今夜逍遥快活 明天分道扬镳
"We got tonight. Who needs tomorrow"?
你什么事都往鲍勃·西格的歌上靠吗
Is everything a Bob Seger song to you?
是啊
Yes.
好吧
Well…
很高兴认识你 佩珀
It was nice knowing you, Piper.
佩珀
Piper?
太赞了
That's awesome.
海瑟 一夜奇迹啊
Heather. One-night wonders, man.
该死 我们还能有这等艳福就算走运了
Shoot, we're lucky we still get that at all.
是吗 你不…
Really? You don't…
想要更多吗
Ever want something more?
抱歉 你认识我们吗
I'm sorry, have you met us?
我们根本没有过上家庭生活的可能性
We're batting a whopping zero in domestic life, man. Goose eggs.
你就不会想吗
You don't ever think about something?
不是婚姻什么的 但是
Not marriage or whatever. But…
比如跟猎人发展段感情
Something? You know, with a hunter?
理解我们这种生活的人
Somebody who understands the life?
你没听到鲍勃歌里的歌词吗
Have you not heard a single word Bob's been singing about?
你累了 我看得出 你是累坏了
You're tired. I can tell. You're exhausted.
我还精神饱满呢
Well, I'm still wired,
我停车去加点油
so I'm gonna pull over, get some gas.
你上后面去睡会儿吧
You hop in the back, get some z's.
你该睡会儿了
'cause, buddy, you earned 'em.
为你骄傲啊 佩珀
Proud of ya! Piper.
而且她好香啊
Man, she smelled good, too.
你听什么呢
What are you listening to?
你妈妈以前可喜欢这首歌了
Your mom used to love this song.
爸爸
Dad?
你没事吧 伙计
You okay, pal?
你像是见鬼了
You look a little spooked.
能重回驾驶席感觉真好
It's nice to be back behind the wheel.
看来迪恩很会照顾这老家伙
Looks like Dean's taken good care of this old beast.
看来他把你照顾得也不错
Seems like he's taken good care of you, too.
这怎么回事 又是幻觉吗
What is this? Another vision?
你最近经常看到幻觉吗 儿子
Are you having visions, son?
别那么喊我
Don't call me that.
怎么了 当爹的还不能喊
What? A father can't call his…
不 我父亲已经死了
No, my father is dead.
死亡什么时候阻挡过温家人
When has death ever stopped a Winchester?
听着 我不知道这怎么回事 但是
Look, I don't know what this is, but…
你之前说的 关于感情的话
What you said about relationships,
想要更深层次的感情
wanting something more…
我根本没想让你们过上这种生活
I never wanted this for you boys.
真的
This life. Not really.
我们过得也还行
We turned out okay.
是啊
You did, didn't you?
但那是你们的努力 你们做到的 不是我
But that was on you boys. You did that, not me.
你也尽了职
Well, you played your part.
我至少是尽了全力
I did my best, anyway,
不管怎么样
for what it was worth.
这不是真的
This isn't real.
我一向都骗不了你
I never could fool you, could I?
我在教堂里时祈祷了
I prayed when I was in that church,
我看到了
And I saw…
什么
Something.
现在 你出现了 不管你是谁
And now, here you are, whoever you are,
不管你是什么
whatever you are.
这是怎么回事
What the hell is this?
梦 幻觉 随你怎么说
Dream. Vision. Call it what you want.
传递的讯息是一样的
The message is still the same.
黑暗要来了
The Darkness is coming…
只有你们能阻止它
And only you boys can stop it.
好吧
Okay, fine.
怎么阻止
How?
我们需要帮助
We need help,
而不是看到死人的幻觉
not visions of dead people.
上帝帮助自助者
God helps those who help themselves.
你是谁
Who are you?
欢迎来到温家旅馆
Welcome to the Winchester motel.
我们没有有线电视 但我们有
We don't have cable, but we do…
客房服务
have room service.
你睡觉时还唱歌了
You were singing in your sleep,
就是妈妈喜欢 爸爸老放给我们听的那首
That song mom loved that dad used to always play for us.
你好像还有那盘带呢
I think I've actually still got the tape.
迪恩
Hey, Dean, um…
你说你看到黑暗时
You said when you saw the Darkness,
你不确定那是…
you weren't sure whether it was, uh…
真的还是幻觉 是吧
the real thing or a vision, right?
我觉得我最近也看到了些幻觉
I think I've been having visions, too, lately.
就是一些画面
I mean, it's just images.
更像是感觉吧
I mean, more of a… feeling, really.
但我刚刚又看到一个
But I just had one.
就刚刚 而且还看到了爸爸
right now, and… and dad was in it.
但不是
But it wasn't dad like… like…
我小时候看到的那个爸爸
the dad that… that I grew up with.
是像我们这么大的那个爸爸
It was dad when he was our age.
我猜那根本都不是爸爸
And I-I guess it wasn't even really dad.
可能是谁装成了爸爸
It was someone pretending to be dad and…
你为什么这么说
Okay, what makes you say that?
首先 他跟我说了一切我想听的话
For starters, he told me everything I wanted to hear.
嗯 听上去不像是爸爸
Yeah, that doesn't sound like dad.
是啊 总之 那个人
No. Anyways, whoever it was…
给我们传递了一则讯息
they had a message to deliver.
那人说黑暗要来了
They said the Darkness is coming,
而且
and…
只有你我能阻止它
only you and I can stop it.
那人给你什么关于怎么阻止它的有用建议了吗
Did they have him give you any helpful tips on how to do that?
他说 「上帝帮助自助者」
He said, "God helps those who help themselves."
或许这幻觉是上帝给的
I mean, maybe these visions are coming from God.
打住
Pump the brakes.
迪恩 第一个幻觉是我祈祷后看到的
I mean, Dean, the first one happened after I prayed.
你祈祷了 什么时候
You prayed? When was this?
在医院的时候
Back in the hospital.
为什么
Why?
因为我被感染了
Because I was infected.
我当时被感染了 现在没事了
I was infected. I'm not anymore.
我也没完全发狂过
I-I-I never went full rabid. I…
我被感染了 居然不告诉我吗
You get infected and you didn't even tell me.
- 迪恩 - 你祈祷什么了
- Dean… - What did you pray about?
我想我就是在寻求答案
I guess I was just looking for answers, you know?
我相信 不管是什么在你脑子里折腾
Well, I'm sure whatever is kicking around in your head right now.
肯定是感染的后遗症
is a side effect from the infection.
就是你没告诉我的那次感染
that you failed to tell me about.
我觉得没那么简单
You know, I don't think it's that simple.
拜托 那句话
Come on, man. That quote?
上帝帮助自助者
"God helps those who help themselves"?
那不是上帝的话 都不在《圣经》里
God didn't say that. That's not even in the bible.
是伊索时期的老谚语
That's an old proverb that dates way back to Aesop.
我也读书啊
I read.
更重要的是 上帝什么时候
And more importantly, when was the last time.
回应过我们的祈祷了
God answered any one of our prayers?
那不是幻觉 萨姆 好吗
It's not a vision, Sam. All right?
就是个热夜之梦而已
It's just some… Some fever dream.
仅此而已
That's all.
至于爸爸 我经常梦到他
And as far as dad goes, I dream about dad all the time.
是吗
You do?
当然了 而且都是一样的
Of course I do. It's usually the same one, too.
我们都坐在车上
We're all in the car.
我坐在驾驶席
I'm sitting in the driver's seat,
爸爸坐在副驾
Dad's sitting shotgun.
但没有猎枪
But there aren't any shotguns.
没有怪物 没有猎魔
There's no monsters. There's no hunting.
都没有 只是
There's none of that. It's just…
他在教我开车
He's teaching me how to drive.
我也不是他当年教我
And, uh, and I'm not little like I was.
开车时那样的小孩子
when he actually taught me how to drive.
我16了 他在帮我拿学习驾照
I'm 16, and he's helping me get my learner's permit.
当然 你坐在后座
Of course, you're in the backseat,
求着想开一把
Just begging to take a turn.
我们停在房前 我们家前
We pull up to the house… the family house…
我停在了车道上 他看着我说
and I park in the driveway, and he looks over and he says,
降落完美 儿子
"Perfect landing, son."
每隔几个月我就会梦一次
I have that dream every couple of months.
还挺让人宽慰的 其实
Kind of comforting, actually.
我总是
I always, uh…
我总是梦到妈妈
I always dream about mom.
一般也都是这样的
Usually the same kind of thing, though.
- 正常生活吗 - 嗯 正常生活
- Normal life? - Yeah. Normal life.
但是 迪恩 刚刚那不是梦
But, Dean, this wasn't just a dream.
真的
I'm telling you.
为什么有人会扮成爸爸
Why would somebody dress up like dad.
就为给你传递个讯息啊
to give you a message?
爸爸啊
I mean, dad.
你可不是总听他的话啊
You don't exactly have a history of listening to what he had to say.
你说黑暗也给了你一条讯息
But you said the Darkness is… is sending messages to you.
或许与黑暗相反的东西
Maybe whatever is the opposite of the Darkness.
给我传递了讯息
is sending messages to me.
你觉得这东西是上帝吗
And you think that this thing is god?
拜托
Come on.
上帝有过多少机会撬开你的脑袋
How many… how many opportunities has God had to crack this pi?ata,
而且地上也没有糖果
and I don't see any candy on the floor, do you?
好吧 或许不是上帝 但我
Okay, then maybe it's not God. But I…
我明白你想做什么
I know what you're trying to do here.
你想找到更深远的意义
You're trying to find some… some greater meaning to it all.
是吧 想把发生的事归咎于命运
Right? Some… Fate to what went down.
但我告诉你 萨姆 黑暗
But I'm telling you, Sam. The Darkness?
是我们的错
It's on us.
没人能帮我们了 更别提上帝
And no one's gonna help us, certainly not god,
我们只能自己想办法
So we'll have to figure this thing out,
我们一向如此
like we always do.
但在那之前
But until then…
我们猎魔
we hunt.
首先就是这个案子
This case for starters,
而这桩案子
which this case is…
可能不是案子
It's just probably nothing.
是啊 可能吧
Yeah, probably nothing.
晚安 混蛋
Goodnight, jerk.
晚安 小婊砸
Night, bitch.
尸检官带我去看了治安官的尸体
The coroner showed me the sheriff's body.
的确是残害得不轻
And, uh, it was mauled all right.
听听 心脏不见
And get this… heart missing,
尸体完全被吸干了血
body completely drained of blood.
怎么 狼人/吸血鬼混血吗
So, what? We're looking at a-a werewolf/vampire hybrid?
跟我说 狼血鬼
Say it with me… a were-pire.
- 不要 - 说嘛
- No. - Come on.
我才不要说
I'm not saying that.
随你了 我打给了小卡 让他查看传说了
Whatever. I called Cass, told him to look into the lore.
你有什么发现
What do you got?
嗯 治安官的接替者
Right, well, uh, the sheriff's replacement…
唐纳利警官
Deputy Donnelly…
不算很聪明 但我复印了一份他的报告
He's not the brightest bulb, but I got a copy of his report.
- 或许他有遗漏 - 探员们
- Maybe he missed something. - Agents.
警官
Deputy.
这就是你的搭档了吧 沃什探员吧
This must be your partner. Agent Walsh, right?
幸会
Pleasure to meet you.
我想感谢你们二位前来
I just want to thank you both for stoppin' by.
我们很感激你们的尽职
We really appreciate your due diligence.
话说 你知道哪里有
Actually, uh, do you know a motel.
我们可以住一晚的旅馆吗
where we can crash for the night?
你们要留下吗
You're stayin'?
嗯 确保没有疏漏
Yeah, just wanna kick all the tires.
唐尼街有家旅馆
Well, uh, there's a motel on Downey.
价位不错
that'll give you a good price.
如果想吃顿好的
And if you're looking for a decent meal,
那就是梅尔姑妈餐厅 在火车站附近
you can't beat Aunt Mel's, down by the train station.
停车位不好找
Parking is a bitch,
但那里有全州最棒的牛排
but it's the best damn steak in the whole state.
你说牛排我就心动了
You had me at "steak."
不错诶
Ohh, all right.
这才像话
Now we're cookin' with gas.
代客泊车
Valet?
不是吧
You… what?
迪恩 代客泊车是常事啊
Dean, people valet park all the time.
享受生活嘛
Come on, live a little.
欢迎来到梅尔姑妈餐厅 这里是
Welcome to Aunt Mel's. Home of the…
听着 杰西 别给我刮了
Yeah, listen, uh, Jessie, not a scratch, okay?
蜘蛛抓到苍蝇了
Spider caught a fly.
我重复 蜘蛛抓到苍蝇了
I repeat, spider caught a fly.
- 快走啊 快点 - 来啦
- Let's go! Come on! - Okay!
太棒了 我们走吧
Hell, yeah. Let's roll!
开始派对吧
Let's get this party started.
天呐
Oh, my god!
是 先生
Yes, sir?
我们就来
We're on our way.
我就来
My way.
你做了什么啊
What did you do?
我会被解雇的
I'm gonna get fired.
- 快走 - 好啦
- Come on! - Okay!
- 快点 我得走了 - 我的包包呢
- I gotta go. Let's go! - Where's my purse?
- 你大概落在自己车上了 - 什么
- You probably just left it in your car. - What?
我得走了 要不得被解雇的
I gotta go! I don't wanna get fired!
不错啊 杰西
Strong work, Jessie.
干得不错
Strong work.
谢谢
Thanks.
接下来去哪
So what's next?
我想跟治安官的遗孀谈谈
I want to, uh, talk to sheriff's widow.
莉莉·马克汉姆
Lily Markham.
或许她了解
Maybe she knows something about.
她丈夫为什么会去林子里
why her husband was out in the woods in the first place.
我送你过去
All right, well, I'll drop you off.
我想去趟发现尸体的林子
I wanna go back to the woods where they found the body.
那些犯罪现场照片不太对劲
Something wasn't right about those crime scene photos.
（卡西迪奥）
小卡 你没事吧
Cass, you okay?
我主要有点困惑
I'm mostly confused.
我不知道橙色跟黑色有什么关系
I'm not sure how orange correlates with black…
怎么就新了
in a way that's new.
别碰网飞了
Step away from the netflix.
- 抱歉 - 没事 我们都连看过
- Sorry. - It's okay. We've all had a binge.
在传说中发现什么了吗
You find anything in the lore?
的确有种吃心吸血的怪物
Well, there is a creature that feeds on hearts and blood.
狼血鬼吗
A were-pire, you might say?
来吧 我知道你想说的
Come on, I know you wanna say it.
在传说中被称为低语
In the lore, it's referred to a whisper.
没劲
That's lame.
银能杀死它
Silver will kill it,
但以防万一还是砍头吧
but you may want to decapitate it just to be sure.
好 听上去不错
All right, sounds good.
我在犯罪现场呢 是布置好的
I'm at the crime scene now. It was staged.
尸体被拖到这儿的 没有挣扎痕迹
The body was dragged. There were no signs of struggle.
是移尸过去伪造成动物袭击的样子吗
Body was moved there to look more like an animal attack?
可能吧 但做得不高明
Yeah, maybe. It was pretty sloppy, though.
你还查到什么了
You, uh…What else you got on these things?
听着 低语有很有趣的历史
Listen to this. Whispers have a fascinating history.
- 等等 - 他们
- Hang on. - They're… they're…
他们曾被认为
actually, they were once believed.
是狼人的后裔
to be in the bloodline of werewolves,
- 但实际上 他们更类似恶魔 - 警官
- but in fact, they are more similar to demons. - Deputy.
- 干什么呢 探员 - 他们
- What's going on, agent? - They, uh,
他们昵称的由来是因为他们出手很安静
they got their nickname from how quiet their attacks are.
由于他们很具隐蔽性
Because of their stealthiness,
已经大隐于市几个世纪了
they've, uh, lived on the fringes for centuries.
但也有几个在塞勒姆女巫时期
Although there were several that were hunted and killed.
被抓到杀死
during the Salem Witch…
等等 好吧 这上面说
Wait a minute. Okay, according to this,
低语只在日食期间进食
whispers only feed during the solar eclipse.
那么 迪恩 你在找的
Uh, so, Dean, I-I don't believe.
应该不是低语了
what you're hunting is a whisper.
肯定是别的什么
Must be another creature of some kind.
好吧 我说
Okay. Fine, I'll say it.
（萨姆来电）
或许是你所谓的「狼血鬼」
Maybe it is your so-called "were-pire."
但老实说 我从没听过
But to be honest, I have never heard…
叫这名字的东西
of a creature with that name.
迪恩 怎么回事
Dean, what is that?
迪恩
Dean?
迪恩 迪恩 你没事吧 我听到了枪声
Dean? Dean, are you all right? I hear gunshots.
迪恩
Dean!
Dean?
迪恩
Dean!
我刚刚枪杀了警官
Ah, it turns out I did shoot the deputy.
等等 迪恩 出什么…
Wait, Dean, is… is everything…
警官是个狼血鬼 没事的
The deputy was a were-pire. It's all right.
银弹起作用了
Silver bullets worked.
不对 迪恩 听我说
No, Dean, listen…
从传说看 时间不对
according to the lore, the timing is off.
距下次北美日食还远着呢
The next solar eclipse in north America is years away.
- 这不可能 - 等下
- It can't be a… - Hang on.
迪恩 等等
Dean, wait.
听着 那不可能是
Listen, it couldn't be…
迪恩
Dean?
当我没说 得砍头…
Scratch that. You gotta cut off their…
迪恩 不是低语
Dean, it's not a whisper.
嗯 我发现了
Yeah, I'm starting to get that.
稍等我下
Give me a second.
好了
All right. Th…
好吧
All right, that…
好了
Okay.
笑一个 混蛋
Smile, asshat.
好了 小卡 在吗
All right, Cass, you there?
当然 怎么回事
Of course. What's going on?
不管是什么 银能拖慢它的速度
Well, whatever it is, silver slows it down.
我正在给你发去一张照片
I, uh, I'm sending you a picture right now…
是它的獠牙
of its fangs.
我从没见过这样的东西
I-I've never seen anything like it.
看看传说中有没有符合的 好吗
See if there's a match in the lore, would ya?
这就去
I'm on it.
（萨姆 需要紧急救援 打给我 萨姆一通未接来电）
（呼叫萨姆）
迪恩 我被袭了
Dean, I got jumped.
- 你没事吧 - 暂时没事了应该
- You okay? - I think… for now.
这应该是一群怪物
Pretty sure we're dealing with a pack here.
我赶到时 有两个正在袭击马克汉姆太太
Uh, two of these things were attacking Mrs. Markham when I arrived.
我打了一堆银弹 但也只是拖慢了他们的速度
I-I filled them with silver, but it only slowed them down.
蠢蛋警官也是一个
Yeah, well, deputy dumbass is one of them as well.
他现在两截了 但还活着
He's, uh, he's in two pieces and still alive.
- 你在哪 - 马克汉姆太太被击昏了
- Where you at now? - Mrs. Markham was knocked out.
我把她抱到附近一间房子了
I-I-I carried her to the house nearby.
我这就把地址发给你
Here, I'll text you the address now.
稳住 我就来
All right, sit tight. I'm on my way.
哥们被袭了
Buddy's gettin' jumped.
我赶到时门就是敞开的
Door was open when I got to the house.
我搜完房子时
By the time I searched through it,
他们已经把她打昏了
they'd already beaten her unconscious.
或许她知道什么
Maybe she knew something.
关于她丈夫的遭遇
or something about what happened to her husband.
怎么 他们想干掉她
So what, they tried to take her out.
而警官则折返去犯罪现场吗
while the deputy went back to the scene?
他想把现场布置好 却碰到了我
Yeah, he went to fix it up. Found me.
小卡 告诉我你有发现
Hey, Cass, tell me you got something.
而且跟小妞进监狱无关
that doesn't involve chicks in prison.
真没想到你会说出这种话
Bet you never thought you'd say that out loud.
是尼塔特
It's a Nachzehrer.
啥玩意儿
Come again?
一种食尸鬼加吸血鬼一类的生物
A ghoul and vampire-like creature.
那就是尸血鬼 对吧
A ghoul-pire! Right?
有的族群吃尸体的腐肉
Some breeds feed on the flesh of the dead.
还有的吃活人的血液和心脏
Others feed on the blood and hearts of the living.
它们是小群体聚居的
They run in small packs,
但通常行事都非常低调
but they usually keep an extremely low profile.
好吧 那怎么才能弄死它们
Great. So how do we kill 'em?
它们已经死了
Well, they're already dead.
换句话说
So in a manner of speaking,
它们只需要被人提醒它们已经死了
they just need to be reminded that they're dead.
你们需要一枚冥神的银币
You need a charon's obol.
对啊
Of course.
在古希腊 当一个人死了
Yeah, in ancient Greece, uh, when a person died,
有的人认为 得放一枚银币 或者硬币
some people believed you had to put an obol, or a-a coin,
在死者嘴里 这样死者就能以此来交换
in their mouth so they can use it as currency.
被摆渡去冥河对岸 进入地下世界
to be taken across the river to the underworld.
没错 你们要往尼塔特嘴里放个硬币
Right, you place a coin in a nachzehrer's mouth,
然后把头割下来 这样就能杀死它们了
then sever their head, and that will kill them.
还有 据说 如果杀掉它们的群头领
And according to the lore, if you kill the pack's alpha,
它们转化的所有人都将恢复为人类
everyone they've turned will revert back to human form.
太好了 好吧 咱们上哪找银币
Awesome. All right, where do we find an obol?
根据记录者的记录
Well, according to the men of letters' records,
你们需要一枚铜板
you're gonna need a copper coin.
他们以前用的是便士 所以你们得去找个来
They used to use pennies, so you'll need one of those.
好吧 可那得是1982年以前的了
Yeah, but one minted pre-1982.
1982年以前 便士含95%的铜
So before 1982, pennies were 95% copper.
后来就改用镀铜锌币了
Since then, they're only copper-plated zinc.
你的书呆子属性简直突破天际
Your nerdiness knows no bounds.
不用谢
You're welcome.
好吧 谢了 小卡
All right, well, thanks Cass.
干得好 你真立功了
Good work. Way to come off the bench.
什么
What bench?
继续疗伤吧 好吗
Just get back to getting better, okay?
我是没有
Got nothing.
是啊 这年头上哪找便士去啊
Well, yeah, I mean, who carries pennies these days anyway?
我去去就回
I'll be right back.
好
Yeah.
马克汉姆太太
Mrs. Markham?
Mrs. Markham.
没事的 我是迪恩·温彻斯特
It's okay. I'm dean winchester.
- 我弟弟萨姆… - 我这是在哪
- My … my brother Sam and… - Where am I?
你被杀死你丈夫的那群人袭击了
You were attacked by the same people that killed your husband.
我丈夫
My husband.
你知道他到底出了什么事吗
Now do you know something about what happened to him?
也许这就是那些人袭击你的原因
Maybe that's why these people attacked you?
好吧 我们会带你去个安全的地方 好吗
Okay. Well, we're gonna take you someplace safe, all right?
然后我们会灭了这群狗娘养的
And then we're gonna kill these sons of bitches.
我可以解释的
I could … uh, I could explain that.
也许还是算了吧
Well, maybe not.
这就是袭击你的那种东西 明白吗
Uh, it's like the thing that attacked you, okay?
它叫尸血鬼
It's … it's a ghoul-pire.
重点是 它不能再伤害你了
The point is, it can't hurt you anymore.
至少我觉得不能了…这么着吧
At least, I don't think it… Let's…You know what?
咱们把它丢掉
Let's just get rid of it.
好了
Here we go.
行了 看到没 没事了
Okay, all right. See? There we go.
你还好吗
You okay?
家人
Your family.
人会为家人做任何事 对吗
You do anything for them, don't you?
当然
Absolutely.
但也不能完全不计代价
Yeah, but not if it costs too much.
不
No.
人就是会为家人不惜一切代价
You do everything for them.
除此之外的一切都毫无意义
Everything else is meaningless.
可我做错了
But I did it wrong.
我毁了一切
Now I've ruined everything.
这不是你的错
This isn't your fault.
我把我的家人置于了险境
I put my family at risk.
它们袭击我是对的
They were right to attack me.
但我知道要怎么弥补
But I know how to make it right.
它在哪
Where is it?!
你把创造者的尸体怎么了
What did you do with the maker's body?!
快告诉我 不然我灭了你
You're gonna tell me or I will end you!
看到没 也没那么难
See? That wasn't so hard.
现在我知道该怎么对付你了
Now I know what to do with you.
*我能弥补这一切*
*I can make this right*
你没事
You're okay.
看 我都解决好了
See? I fixed it.
你没事了
You're okay.
我知道你醒了
I know you're awake.
我知道你是猎人
I know you're a hunter.
我也知道你是尼塔特
And I know you're a nachzehrer.
创造者 对吗 群领头
The maker, right? The pack Alpha?
你也不像看上去那么傻嘛
Well, maybe you're not as dumb as you look.
你们不是喜欢保持低调的吗
Thought you and yours like to keep a low profile.
可惜 莉莉这种菜鸟
Sadly, rookies like Lily here aren't up to snuff.
不太会进食
when it comes to keeping their feeding quiet.
这么说是你杀死了自己的丈夫
So you killed your husband?
他不愿意加入我们
He wouldn't join us.
不愿意加入的人就是食物
People who don't join are food.
但是我搞砸了 我没埋好他
But I messed up, and I… I didn't bury him right.
这其实是我的错
It's my fault, really.
你还没训练好
You weren't properly trained.
但人人都该有第二次机会嘛
but everyone deserves a mulligan, don't they?
这就是我的人想做的事 莉莉
That's all my people were trying to do, Lily.
他们不是去杀你的
They weren't going to kill you.
我需要你啊
Hell, I need you.
我需要一切可以得到的帮助
I need all the help I can get.
你转化了多少人
Have many have you turned?
头一百年吗 三个人
In the first hundred years? Three.
这三个月 16个
In the last month? 16.
干吗 你要组个棒球队还是怎样
What, are you trying to field a baseball team?
我说过了 我需要帮助
It's like I said, I need help,
我能找到的所有力量
every strong hand I can find.
我需要一支军队
And I need an army.
对抗黑暗
to fight the Darkness.
它要来了 冲我们所有人来
Oh, it's comin', for all of us.
任何猎人和人类都没办法对抗它
There's nothing hunters or any human can do about it.
你知道怎么阻止它吗
Do you know how to stop it?
我觉得没什么能阻止它
I don't think anything can stop it.
我只是想争取一些时间
I'm just tryin' to buy some time,
所以我在努力转化尽可能多的男男女女
so I'm turning as many strong men and women as I can.
你弟弟会成为军中不错的新添力量
Your brother will make a fine addition to the rank and file.
在你昏迷期间
While you slept,
我用你的手机给他发了条短信
I send him a text message from your phone.
他现在正往陷阱里钻呢
Oh, he's heading into a trap right now.
你本来也能做个优秀的士兵
You'd make a good soldier, too,
但你砍掉了我的头 这个我可忍不了
but you cut off my head, and I can't stand for that.
别担心
Don't worry.
我是那种物尽其用的人
I'm an every part of the buffalo kind of guy.
你的死不会白白浪费的
Your death won't go to waste.
你会成为你弟弟的第一餐
You'll be your brother's first meal.
宝贝 真抱歉
Oh, baby, I'm so sorry.
天哪 我都做了什么
Oh, my God. What have I…
我的孩子
My kids.
我的孩子们 他们转化了我的孩子
My kids. They turned my kids.
他们跟其他人在一起 拜托你
They're with the others. Please.
萨姆
Sam.
好
Yeah, yeah.
启动啊 启动啊
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
给点力啊 宝贝 好了
Come on, baby. Yeah! There we go.
坐稳
Hang on.
妈妈
Mom!
你没事吧
You okay?
「可能不是案子」 是吧
Probably nothing, right?
大家都没事吧
Everybody all right back there?
嗯 他们都变回来了
Uh, yeah. They all changed back.
是那个蠢蛋警官 对吗
So it was Deputy dumbass, huh?
对 蠢蛋警官
Yeah, Deputy dumbass.
他想组建军队来着
You know, he was trying to build an army.
我知道
Yeah, I know,
为了对抗黑暗
to fight the Darkness.
迪恩 连怪物都吓坏了
Dean, even the monsters are scared.
让他们怕去好了
Well, let 'em be.
你和我
You and I,
咱们这就了结了这一切
we're gonna end this thing now.
明天再开始 你不介意吧
Would you mind starting tomorrow?
同意
Deal.
那好
我们去找小卡把你治好
We'll get Cass to fix you up.
除非他也把你治好
Only if he fixes you up, too.
行啊 老妈
Okay, mom.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
知道吗
You know what?
我们已经在家了
We are home.
加油 加油
Come on. Come on.
这才是我的宝贝
There's my girl.